<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView  xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".views.TermsAndConditionsActivity">
    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical"
        tools:ignore="MissingConstraints">
        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/txtTermsAndConditions"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="16dp"
            android:layout_marginHorizontal="16dp"
            android:text="Terms and conditions Favore"
            android:textSize="24sp"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
            app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.5"
            app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
            app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="16dp"
            android:layout_marginHorizontal="16dp"
            android:textSize="20sp"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:text="Service Terms Conditions and Privacy Protection" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginHorizontal="16dp"
            android:layout_marginTop="16dp"
            android:text="We are Monitech  a company registered in Peru at UPC, Lima, Lima 15073. We operate the mobile application Favore , as well as any other related products and services that refer or link to these legal terms (the Legal Terms) (collectively, the Services). \nYou can contact us by phone at 1800665534, email at contact@monitech.com, or by mail to UPC, Lima, Lima 15073, Peru. \nThese Legal Terms constitute a legally binding agreement made between you, whether personally or on behalf of an entity (you), and Monitech, concerning your access to and use of the Services. You agree that by accessing the Services, you have read, understood, and agreed to be bound by all of these Legal Terms. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ALL OF THESE LEGAL TERMS, THEN YOU ARE EXPRESSLY PROHIBITED FROM USING THE SERVICES AND YOU MUST DISCONTINUE USE IMMEDIATELY. \nWe will provide you with prior notice of any scheduled changes to the Services you are using. The modified Legal Terms will become effective upon posting or notifying you by info@monitech.com, as stated in the email message. By continuing to use the Services after the effective date of any changes, you agree to be bound by the modified terms. \nThe Services are intended for users who are at least 18 years old. Persons under the age of 18 are not permitted to use or register for the Services. \nWe recommend that you print a copy of these Legal Terms for your records."
            android:textSize="16sp" />

        <Button
            android:id="@+id/btnAccept"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="16dp"
            android:layout_marginHorizontal="16dp"
            android:text="Accept"
            android:textSize="20sp"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:textColor="@color/white"
            android:onClick="onAcceptTermsAndConditions"
            />
    </LinearLayout>

</ScrollView >